

CONTACT



Born 1984



3rd district 4th Area 6 of October



+20 106 122 7558



ehabterra@hotmail.com



@ehabterra
github.com/ehabterra



https://www.linkedin.com/in/ehab terra-271b3a23/

SKILLS

R language

Python, Numpy, Pandas, matplotlib, PS4

Apache Spark

Hadoop

Elastic search

HTML, CSS3 and JavaScript

Node.js and TypeScript

Golang

C#

Also proficient in SQL Server, Angular 8, Latex, and Docker, grew up bilingual (Arabic and English).

EHAB MOHAMED ELSAYED TERRA

SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER AND ALENGINEER

I have more than 12 years of experience in software development, I involved in the full-stack development of web applications using C#, NodeJs, Golang,...etc for the back-end and AngularJS for the front-end. Beside that, I was publishing researches in the topics of text clustering and feature selection mainly using R as a part of the Master Degree.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Developer - Freelancing

since April 2020

Using Golang and Elasticsearch to build insight website. Also, involved in other projects using C#, Angular 8, NodeJS, Typescript and ElectronJS.

Senior Software Developer - Ignite (Remote – Netherlands)

October 2016 - December 2019

Build new features and maintenance websites, services and tools for job vacancies websites in Netherlands and other countries.

Senior Software Developer - Comex

October 2014 - October 2016

Responsible for building a web application for reporting, sales, purchases, warehouses, and real estate.

Senior Software Developer - Hindawi

November 2012 - October 2014

Responsible for Back office website for publishing books and articles.

Senior Software Developer - MENA Software (Remote – Bulgaria)

February 2012 - November 2012

Developing Games Portals, Administrations and Gates websites.

Developer - TeBAS, True Technology

2004 - 2009

Developed a web and desktop applications for Personnel (HR, Time Attendance, Payroll), Hospital, POS and Restaurant.

EDUCATION

Master of Computer Science

October 2014 - November 2020, Major in Text Clustering and Data Mining, Cairo University.

Higher Diploma

2009 - 2011, Major in Computer Science, Cairo University.

Bachelor of Commerce

2002 - 2006, Major in Accounting, Ain Shams University.